import { ActionMode } from "./types";

export const COLOR_PALETTES = [
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#00BCD4", back: "#0097A7" }, // Cyan
    { front: "#FF6B6B", back: "#E95555" }, // Red
    { front: "#009688", back: "#00796B" }, // Teal
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#8BC34A", back: "#689F38" }, // Light Green
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#00BCD4", back: "#0097A7" }, // Cyan
    { front: "#FF6B6B", back: "#E95555" }, // Red
    { front: "#009688", back: "#00796B" }, // Teal
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#8BC34A", back: "#689F38" }, // Light Green
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#00BCD4", back: "#0097A7" }, // Cyan
    { front: "#FF6B6B", back: "#E95555" }, // Red
    { front: "#009688", back: "#00796B" }, // Teal
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#8BC34A", back: "#689F38" }, // Light Green
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#00BCD4", back: "#0097A7" }, // Cyan
    { front: "#FF6B6B", back: "#E95555" }, // Red
    { front: "#009688", back: "#00796B" }, // Teal
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#8BC34A", back: "#689F38" }, // Light Green
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#00BCD4", back: "#0097A7" }, // Cyan
    { front: "#FF6B6B", back: "#E95555" }, // Red
    { front: "#009688", back: "#00796B" }, // Teal
    { front: "#F4A940", back: "#D88C2A" }, // Orange
    { front: "#8BC34A", back: "#689F38" }, // Light Green
   
   
]

export const FREE_WORK_ACTION: ActionMode = 'free-work';
export const FREE_WORK_FLIPPED_ACTION: ActionMode = 'free-work-flipped';
export const COMBINED_OPERATIONS_ACTION: ActionMode = 'combined-operations';
export const DOUBLE_CALCULATION_ACTION: ActionMode = 'double-calculation';
export const DOUBLE_CALCULATION_FLIPPED_ACTION: ActionMode = 'double-calculation-flipped';
export const RANDOM_NUMBERS_ACTION: ActionMode = 'random-numbers';
export const RANDOM_NUMBERS_ROTATED_ACTION: ActionMode = 'random-numbers-rotated';
export const PARENTHESES_ACTION: ActionMode = 'parentheses';
export const EQUATION_ACTION: ActionMode = 'equation';
export const PERCENTAGE_ACTION: ActionMode = 'percentage';
export const MONEY_ACTION: ActionMode = 'money';
export const MULTIPLE_MONEY_ACTION: ActionMode = 'multiple-money';
export const TIME_ACTION: ActionMode = 'time';
export const LENGTH_ACTION: ActionMode = 'length';
export const MASS_ACTION: ActionMode = 'mass';
export const SIMPLE_MULTIPLICATION_ACTION: ActionMode = 'simple-multiplication';
export const SIMPLE_DIVISION_ACTION: ActionMode = 'simple-division';
export const SQUARE_ACTION: ActionMode = 'square';
export const REMAINDER_DIVISION_ACTION: ActionMode = 'remainder-division';
export const SQUARE_ROOT_ACTION: ActionMode = 'square-root';
export const MUSICAL_INSTRUMENTS_ACTION: ActionMode = 'musical-instruments';
export const ANIMAL_SOUNDS_ACTION: ActionMode = 'animal-sounds';


export const ACTION_TYPES: ActionMode[] = [
    FREE_WORK_ACTION,
    FREE_WORK_FLIPPED_ACTION,
    COMBINED_OPERATIONS_ACTION,
    DOUBLE_CALCULATION_ACTION,
    DOUBLE_CALCULATION_FLIPPED_ACTION,
    RANDOM_NUMBERS_ACTION,
    RANDOM_NUMBERS_ROTATED_ACTION,
    PARENTHESES_ACTION,
    EQUATION_ACTION,
    PERCENTAGE_ACTION,
    MONEY_ACTION,
    MULTIPLE_MONEY_ACTION,
    TIME_ACTION,
    LENGTH_ACTION,
    MASS_ACTION,
    SIMPLE_MULTIPLICATION_ACTION,
    SIMPLE_DIVISION_ACTION,
    SQUARE_ACTION,
    REMAINDER_DIVISION_ACTION,
    SQUARE_ROOT_ACTION,
    MUSICAL_INSTRUMENTS_ACTION,
    ANIMAL_SOUNDS_ACTION,
]

